(Bernadette:)where they do afternoon tea.
(Bernadette:)Afternoon tea,
how sophisticated of us.
(Penny:)All right, if we're gonna be fancy,
(Penny:)I should probably put on
clean underwear.
La-Dee-Da!
Look who has clean underwear.
(Penny:)No, we're gonna stop at Target
on the way.
(Raj:)Since Sheldon's
not going to Comic-Con,
(Raj:)maybe we could find a cool trio
to dress up as.
(Leonard:)What if we go as The Fantastic Four,
and just tell people
(Leonard:)that The Invisible Girl
is standing there with us.
(Howard:)Oh, and I thought our days
of pretending
(Howard:)to be with women
who don't exist were over.
(Sheldon:)Gentlemen, I am one step away
(Sheldon:)from securing a huge guest
for my convention.
(Leonard:)Does that step include chloroform
and a roll of duct tape?
(Sheldon:)I don't think that will be necessary
for Mr. James Earl Jones.
(Sheldon:)You heard me.
The voice of Darth Vader,
(Sheldon:)the Lion King's dad,
(Sheldon:)and FYI, the guy who says,
"This is CNN."
(Sheldon:)Which also sounds like Darth Vader.